Prozorov Misha

26 April 1990 Kyiv myhajlo.prozorov@gmail.com



.NET Developer

Summary

For a little more than 8 years of commercial development experience, in addition to implement of new features and solving bugs of various levels of complexity. I have proposed and I have implemented solutions to real business problems. I am not conflict and flexible - I am glad for constructive criticism and I am open to discussions in order to make a really good product. I regularly learn - I study new technologies and approaches and try to apply them, if it really will be useful. Also, I share experience with my colleges and students.

Work experience

April 2013 – Current (8 years, 5 months)

C#/.NET developer

April 2021 - Current (5 months)

ChemSpace.com

Chemical marketplace

ChemSpace is a young non-IT company that was founded several years ago with a small team. I try to be proactive and help team when it has a trouble.

I configured CI/CD by Jenkins, deployed and configured Graylog, Prometheus, Graphana on premise and Application Insights in Azure for monitoring and logging.

Technologies: Mongo, Docker, Docker Swarm, .NET 5. For the first time I use Linux as a server so I am becoming familiar with Linux software such as SSH, bash, vim etc.

C#/.NET Mentor

September 2020 - August 2021 (11 months)

FoxmindEd

Education Company

Education of people with has no match experience to get software development skills. Students teach .NET 5, and apply SOLID, DDD, Unit testing and other development practices via code review. It was a hobby - I spent less than 1 hour every day.

Back-end developer

July 2020 - March 2021 (8 months)

Newgrounds

Healthcare Software Solution

As part of the development, some services were written from scratch, some services were ported to .NET Core. In January 2021, our team took over a half-working product from a team of not very talented Indian colleagues, the product had already been launched into production. The main tasks were related to fixing bugs, covering API by tests, also transferring the service to .NET 5.

Technologies: .NET Core, .NET Framework, Web API, Swagger, OData, xUnit, EF6, EF Core, MS SQL, Azure Service Bus, Azure Service Fabric, Identity Server, CI - Azure DevOps, CD - Azure DevOps

Back-end developer

March 2019 - May 2020 (1 year 2 months)

robota.ua

Job search site

The company was created 20 years ago. A lot of legacy code has accumulated since. In the development of new functionality, some services was rewritten and optimized, some services was written from scratch, some services was ported to .NET Core. Such as, one service completes in 3-10 minutes instead of 6 hours before.

I built and integrated a new back-end product for customer service using Kafka and GraphQL.

Technologies: .NET Core, .NET Framework, ASP Web API, Swagger, Identity Server, Dapper, MS SQL, Elasticsearch, Redis, Kafka, Google Cloud Kubernetes, Azure Application Insights, CI - Bitbucket, CD – Octopus

.NET developer

April 2017 - November 2018 (1 year 8 months)

Moneyveo.ua

Payday loans by online

It's the first mine big employer. The company grew well fast therefore I had opportunity to fix performance bottlenecks, to develop interesting features and to fix some strange bugs, etc.

Technologies: NET 4.7.1, ASP MVC, ASP Web API, JQuery, NHibernate, MS SQL, MongoDB, DotTrace, dump analysis, AWS Lambda + AWS SES

Education

National Aviation University (Kyiv)

2007-2013

Computer Science

Languages

English - A2

I can be interviewed

German - A1